let questionArr = [
  {
    question: "What are the names of our Bootcamp Web Dev dogs?",
    correctAnswer: "Tove and Loui",
    wrongAnswer1: "Tom and Jerry",
    wrongAnswer2: "Alfa and Dalula"
  },
  {
    question: "HTML - what is true for a block level element?",
    correctAnswer: "&lt;section&gt; is a block level element",
    wrongAnswer1: "only take up as much space as necessary",
    wrongAnswer2: "both answers are true"
  },
  {
    question:
      "HTML - Which of the following are empty tag(s), meaning no closing tag is needed?",
    correctAnswer: "&lt;br&gt; tag",
    wrongAnswer1: "&lt;a&gt; tag",
    wrongAnswer2: "both tags are empty tags"
  },
  {
    question:
      "CSS - Choose the correct selector specificity in a descending order?",
    correctAnswer: "Inline &gt; ID &gt; Class &gt; Type",
    wrongAnswer1: "Inline &gt; Class > ID &gt; Type",
    wrongAnswer2: "ID &gt; Class &gt; Inline &gt; Type"
  },
  {
    question:
      "CSS - given the following properties. Choose the only valid option to CSS …",
    correctAnswer: "align-self: center",
    wrongAnswer1: "direction-flex: row;",
    wrongAnswer2: "text-color: white;"
  },
  {
    question: "JS - For an interpolation of a variable in a string, we use …",
    correctAnswer: "backticks",
    wrongAnswer1: "square bracket",
    wrongAnswer2: "single quotes "
  },
  {
    question: "JS - What is true about the .includes() method?",
    correctAnswer: "returns a boolean",
    wrongAnswer1: "it is not case sensitive",
    wrongAnswer2: "does not work on strings "
  },
  {
    question: "JS - The return number of .localeCompare method is …",
    correctAnswer: "-1 if reference string is before compared string ",
    wrongAnswer1: "1 if reference string is before compared string",
    wrongAnswer2: "depends on the length of the string"
  },
  {
    question: "JS -Choose the correct statement of the logical operators", //prüfen
    correctAnswer: "!(4 &gt; 2) 	// =&gt; false",
    wrongAnswer1: "false && (anything) is a short-circuit evaluated to true",
    wrongAnswer2: "true || false // =&gt; false"
  },
  {
    question: "JS - What is the difference between .slice() and .substring()",
    correctAnswer: ".slice() also supports a negative number",
    wrongAnswer1: "there is no difference, they can be used equivalently",
    wrongAnswer2: ".substring() also supports a negative number"
  },
  {
    question:
      "JS - Boolean, undefined, symbol and null. Which of this are primitives and immuntable?",
    correctAnswer: "they all are primitives and immutable",
    wrongAnswer1: "boolean and null",
    wrongAnswer2: "undefined and null"
  },
  {
    question: "JS - Which of the following advanced methods will mutate an array ?",
    correctAnswer: ".reverse() and.forEach",
    wrongAnswer1: ".map(), .filter() and.reduce()",
    wrongAnswer2: ".forEach() and.map()"
  },
  {
    question: "When it comes to programming what is TDD associated with?",
    correctAnswer: "it refers to software testing and its approach is to write the tests before writing the code",
    wrongAnswer1: "it refers to software testing and its approach is to write the tests after writing the code",
    wrongAnswer2: " it refers to Time Defined Designing"
  },
  {
    question: "When creating a class, the constructor is a special method ...",
    correctAnswer: "used to create the instance objects.",
    wrongAnswer1: "used to create objects different structure.",
    wrongAnswer2: "can be used several times in a class"
  },
  {
    question: "An anonymous function ...",
    correctAnswer: "is not accessible after its creation if no variable assigned to it",
    wrongAnswer1: "can be used as a parameter passed to another function",
    wrongAnswer2: "all answers are correct "
  },
  {
    question: "Which command is used to view all commits made in the past ..",
    correctAnswer: "git log",
    wrongAnswer1: "git commit",
    wrongAnswer2: "git status"
  },
  {
    question: "Thank you for planing!",
    correctAnswer: "O1",
    wrongAnswer1: "O2",
    wrongAnswer2: "O3"
  }
];
